# Summary

Determined full-stack engineer who loves learning in a fast paced environment and the ability to contribute to a team. E-commerce experience and a challenging Turing School education combine to make a better leader and developer with regards to product innovation and user focus.

## **Skills**

#### **Technical**

| Javascript | ••••  |
|------------|-------|
| CSS        | ••••  |
| HTML       | ••••  |
| React      | ••••  |
| Redux      | ••000 |
| Node.js    | ••000 |
| Git        | ••000 |
|            |       |

#### **Professional**

| Activator     | •••• |
|---------------|------|
| Hustler       | •••• |
| Creativity    | •••• |
| Organization  | •••• |
| Adaptability  | •••• |
| Strategic     | •••• |
| Communication | •••• |

## Education

# Turing School of Software and Design

- Student Advisory Board leader

## Indiana University of Indianapolis

- BA Economics
- Kelley School of Business

# Experience

## **Arbor Anglers**

2019 - Present

Assistant Manager

 Sales focused. Develops marketing strategies to increase brand recognition and customer loyalty

## Fly Lords

2018 - Present

Travel Photographer

- Destination Photographer for ad campaigns with major brands in the fly fishing and outdoors industries
- Attract and land new clients through both digital networking and industry events

# The Loki Project

2017 - Present

Web Administrator and Customer Support

- Design and manage wordpress and shopify ecommerce platforms
- Developed our best selling product (Lightroom Presets) and handled all customer support

## Projects

jessepackwood.com/projects

Coin Watch React, Redux, Firebase, SCSS

https://github.com/jessepackwood/CoinWatch

Cryptocurrency tracking web app that pulls the coincap.io api to watch specific coin performance and track the value of a user generated portfolio. The data is stored in Google Firebase and stored in the front end with Redux.

## Movie Tracker React, Redux, Postgres, SCSS

https://github.com/katiescruggs/movie-tracker-frontend

Web app utilizing the movieDB api to pull the most recently released films so a user can sign in and favorite films to their personal account. User accounts are stored in PostgreSQL.

## **SWapiBox** React, Jest

https://github.com/jessepackwood/swapiBox

Star Wars api is used to render data about the movies series characters, vehicles, and planets.